Stop it! Both of you!
(Sheldon:)This fighting, I might as well be back
with my parents.
[AS MOTHER] "I told you if you didn't
quit drinking, I'd leave you."
[AS FATHER] "I guess that makes you a liar.
I'm drunk as hell and you're still here."
[AS MOTHER] "Stop yelling.
You're making Sheldon cry."
[AS FATHER]
"I'll tell you what's making Sheldon cry.
That I let you name him Sheldon."
(Howard:)Boy, what got him so upset?
(Raj:)Oh, sure. You can tell
when Sheldon's upset.
(Penny:)Oh. Thank you very much.
Come back soon.
(Penny:)With the other half of my tip.
[SIGHS]
(Penny:)Hey, Sheldon.
What're you doing here?
(Sheldon:)This is a restaurant. It's lunchtime.
I'd think as a waitress you'd be familiar
with the paradigm.
(Penny:)-Is Leonard coming?
-No.
(Sheldon:)I believe Leonard is waiting for you
to come back to him and apologize.